passionsearch.com 2004-08-16

# freeiPods.com

Protecting your privacy is important to us. We hope the following statement will help you understand how freeiPods.com collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on our Web site.

  * We respect your privacy and will not send you anything in the mail you haven't ordered. 
  * Our iPod players come with a full warranty. Our supplier(s) will also safeguard your personal information and not give it out to other parties for any reason. They will not have access to any referral information you provide.

To create an account with the freeiPods.com, we collect your name, email address, and a shipping address. We use this information to set up your account, to send you a registration confirmation email and log your shipping information so we know where to send your order. We also give you a password that you may change in the Account page of our site. We will send you active emails thanking you for joining, sending a verification link, telling you an order has shipped, etc. We may also use your email address to send you information about new services, features, and special offers from us. Members may opt-out of receiving these types of future mailings by following instructions in the newsletter.

All email addresses for referrals, contest information and survey answers are securely protected. freeiPods.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

We may send you offers on behalf of our business partners. Keep in mind that if you take advantage of an offer from a freeiPods.com business partner and become their customer, they may independently wish to send offers to you. In this case, you will need to inform them separately if you wish to decline receiving future offers from them.

Our goal is to deliver offers to people who we believe will find them of value. Offers are developed and managed under strict conditions designed to safeguard the security and privacy of customer personal information.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. freeiPods.com uses cookies to better understand your traffic patterns through the Web site. This information helps us improve the navigation and flow of the Web site. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future.

Please note that we can only allow one account per household. We do this to protect our advertising partners, and help to ensure quality leads, and not allow a single person to complete an offer more than once. For anyone who lives in a household with multiple people, we recommend you share an account.

This Privacy Policy applies to consumers that have signed up on the freeiPods.com website. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may work with other third party businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members via direct mail, email and telemarketing. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation and email marketing.
